9rules.com 2007-12-11

# 9rules - Terms of Service

### Terms & Service

Welcome to 9rules. We want everyone to have a good time and for 9rules to be a safe place for people to communicate online. To ensure this standard we have rules in place for using the 9rules site. 

Protecting the privacy of minors is especially important. For that reason, by using 9rules you agree that you are atleast 14 years old.

Using 9rules, you agree you understand our policies and you agree to them. 9rules will not be held responsible for the user-created content and activities on the site. You acknowledge and agree that all content (text and media) publicly or privately transmitted are the sole responsibility of the individual posting the content, not 9rules.

9rules reserves the right to add, remove or change any feature on the site at any time without notice or liaibility.

### Code of Conduct

To use my.9rules, you will have to create a username and supply your email address. Your password will be sent to you. Please be aware that you are responsible for your activities online and the confidentiality of your password. If you change your password, chose a secure one with upper and lower case letters and at least one number. You have the option of submitting other information to customize your profile page for example your RSS feed, Flickr stream, etc.

To ensure a safe browsing experience we recommend:

  * You keep your contact information (email address) current.
  * You [contact us immediately](http://9rules.com/about/contact) if you suspect malicious activity on your account.
  * Do not exchange personal information with anyone you do not know. If you decide to meet with a user offline meet in a public place and tell a guardian, a friend or family member where you are going.
  * That you logout after each session. 

The internet is a great tool for meeting people, learning things and having fun. You might not agree with some of the things you read on 9rules, but we expect users to have mutual respect for each other.

  * 9rules reserves the right to remove discussions that encourage racism, bigotry, violence, hatred, profanity, or that have no substantive value.
  * 9rules reserves the right to remove offensive and inappropriate discussions that violate our Code of Conduct.
  * Spam and blatant self-promotion are not tolerated on 9rules.
  * Content posted full-text into a Topic or Notes discussion is not permitted, even if you are the author of the content. Please quote from the article if needed but do not copy and paste content from another site directly into a Topic or Notes discussion. We consider this spam. [Read more about what we consider spam and self-promotion.](http://9rules.com/The%20rulers/notes/5702/)
  * You cannot use 9rules to distribute or post illegal items or information or post to sites that engage in those activities.
  * If you want to share files with the community, for example a design template, movie or podcast, do not link to the file directly. Link to download page for the file(s) so our users can be fully informed about what they are downloading. It is your responsibiliy to check those files for viruses, trojans, etc.
  * You are responsible for your actions and activities on 9rules, and we may ban users who violate our Terms of Service.
  * You are responsible for protecting your computer. We recommend installing a reliable virus protection program.

### Privacy Policy - Effective February 2007

9rules values your privacy and this document will help you understand the information that is collected when you use 9rules and make informed decisions when using the site.

### The Information We Collect

When you browse 9rules, a cookie is placed on your computer unless you have this feature disabled in your browser. A cookie is a small data file that sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that grants you access to areas of the site, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. 9rules uses cookies to track user traffic patterns and to allow you to access areas of the 9rules site that require login information.

While browsing 9rules the following general non-identifying information is collected automatically (this happens when you visit any site): your IP address, the browser you are using, the pages you viewed, the date you viewed them and possibly the referrer (if you visit the 9rules site by clicking on a link from another site, like Google, this information is called referrer information. The site you previously visited).

### How We Use The Information

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our site and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our site, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but 9rules will not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

### Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Accessing or Correcting Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that you submitted to us via your my.9rules profile page. In this area you can view and edit this information at any time.

### Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, [send us an email.](http://9rules.com/about/contact)

"9rules has the power of both exclusivity and continued expectation. Neither the social news networks nor Squidoo have this going for them." -[Rick Turoczy](http://morethanaliving.com/blog)

A beautiful clay representation of the 9rules logo that one of our fans put together: [image](http://img83.imageshack.us/img83/967/9rulesxn5.jpg).

"I'm shocked. I just found out that I was accepted into 9Rules!. [...] Since I’ve been blogging, 9 Rules has kind of been that lofty white peak that you hope to reach, but think you will." -[Josh](http://system13.org/2006/12/14/me-in-9rules-how-can-that-be/)

"OMG! I’ve been accepted into the 9Rules blog network!! I’m so excited!" -[Manga Maniac Cafe](http://www.mangamaniaccafe.com/?p=1569)

"I am now a proud member of the 9rules Network. Can I explain how happy that makes me? Can I? Because it makes me really freaking happy." -[Cranky Mama](http://www.cranky-mama.com/?p=192)
